wowthemes.net 2019-04-06

# Privacy Policy | Wow Themes

**Our Privacy Policy has been updated for the GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation) compliance on May 22, 2018.**

## Who we are

[WowThemes.net](https://wowthemes.net/) (this “Website”) is delivered and operated by WOW DEVELOPMENT, RO34450484 (our “Company”). We are committed to protecting the privacy of all personal information obtained from you during any visits to this website. By using our website, you indicate that you read and you agree with our privacy policy below.

## Information we collect and how we use it

This Website may collect and process personal and non personal data that you provide to us. Personal data as defined by GDPR means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person. This Website may collect and process personal and non personal data through:

### Contact/Ticket submission forms

Each time you contact us, a ticket is automatically created. We collect questions, queries or feedback you leave, including your name, email address, website URL, item licenses or other info you may provide in your message box. We use these details to respond to the feedback/query you send us.

**We automatically** : * delete tickets after 120 days * delete tickets with status “deleted” after 30 days * delete ticket files after 120 days * delete ticket feedback after 30 days unless we have your explicit consent to publish it on this Website

### Chat forms

Each time you contact us via chat, we collect questions, queries or feedback you leave, including your name, email address, website URL, item licenses or other info you may provide in chat. We use these details to communicate in chat or to respond to the feedback/query you send us if a ticket is automatically created.

**We automatically** : * delete customer chats after 30 days * delete bot chats after 30 days * delete operator chats after 30 days * delete group chats after 30 days * delete chat files after 30 days * delete ticket feedback after 30 days unless we have your explicit consent to publish it on this Website

### Newsletter subscription forms

We collect your name and email address when you sign-up to receive our monthly email newsletter. In addition to our monthly newsletter, we may periodically send additional emails, which we think you may find useful (such as blog articles, theme updates, new product releases, discounts, changes to our service). If you’ve signed up for email alerts, you can unsubscribe at any time by selecting the “unsubscribe” link that appears in every email we send. We will never share your information other than for the purpose for which it was provided to us.

### Google forms

We collect feedback through google forms. We collect personal information such as name and email address and other non personal information such as product used, rating and feedback. Your feedback is confidential unless we have your explicit consent to publish it on this Website.

### Affiliate sign-up forms

The technology for this Website affiliate campaign is provided by a third party - [Impact](https://impact.com/privacy-policy/). Impact products are fully compliant with the GDPR.

### Payment processing forms

The technology for this Website e-commerce activities is provided by a third party - [FastSpring](https://fastspring.com/features/payment-methods-and-security/). FastSpring is fully compliant with the GDPR.

### Website Analytics

To improve your experience on our site, we may use ‘cookies’. Cookies are an industry standard and most major web sites use them. A cookie is a small text file that our site may place on your computer as a tool to remember your preferences. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.

Our website uses LiveZilla visitor tracking ( a self hosted platform) and Google Analytics, a service which transmits website traffic data to Google servers in the United States. Google Analytics does not identify individual users or associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. We use reports provided by Google Analytics to help us understand website traffic and webpage usage.

By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner described in [Google’s Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/) and for the purposes set out above. You can opt out of Google Analytics if you disable or refuse the cookie, disable JavaScript, or use the [opt-out service provided by Google](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

For website analytics, we collect: \- The pages you visited, when (date and time) you visited them and how long you visited them for \- The website address from which you accessed this site \- The website address from which you exited this site \- Queries via the site’s search engine \- Internet browser and devices used \- Information on how you use the site, through cookies.

Livezilla’s visitor history is automatically set to be deleted after 1 day.

Our Google Analytics data retention is set for 14 months.

We honor Do Not Track signals and do not track or plant cookies when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

## E-Commerce

### How do we process payments?

All transactions are processed through our gateway provider [FastSpring](https://fastspring.com/features/payment-methods-and-security/). Transactions are not stored or processed on our servers.

### PCI Compliance

FastSpring addresses all PCI compliance issues, and securely processes sensitive data. All FastSpring stores are PCI compliant, and adhere to PCI DSS regulations. FastSpring’s entire e-commerce infrastructure is regularly monitored and credit card numbers are never stored.

### Fraud Protection

FastSpring protects companies from fraud by automatically analyzing every order in real time using FastSpring’s proprietary fraud screening technology.

## External Links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party links on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. We are not responsible for the content of any linked website and cannot take responsibility for the consequences of your using the information or services on linked websites. We cannot guarantee that these links will work all of the time. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

This Website uses interfaces with social media sites such as Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter and others. If you choose to “like” or “share” information from this website through these services, you should review the privacy policy of that service.

We embed external content from third-party websites such as YouTube. This content is not published on this Website. It is delivered using devices and services provided by such third party sites that can be inserted into our site. We are not responsible for this content.

## External Links to our Product Demos

WowThemes.net creates free and premium themes, templates, plugins and scripts. The products usually have a website demo assigned. Demos are hosted on various domains which we own. The current privacy policy applies, except no personal data is used.

We store data via contact forms, subscribe forms, comments but we never use them. Product demo websites have no real purpose other than introducing a product’s design and/or functionality. We assume you are only testing the functionality of that specific product while submitting the forms thus we never use your data in response. However, you can of course exercise your GDPR rights.

## Third-Party Disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information. We may also release information when its release is appropriate to comply with and forced by the law.

**Non** -personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for (re)marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## Breach Notifications

We use SSL encryption in the transmission of your personal information between your system and ours. However, no system can be completely secure. No method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and we are unable to guarantee the absolute security of the Personal Information we have collected from you.

If our Website experiences a data breach we will immediately communicate this to those users affected by the breach. A notification will be sent within 72 hours to all affected users.

## Your rights

### Right to information

This right provides the data subject with the ability to ask a company for information about what personal data is being processed and the rationale for such processing.

### Right to access

This right provides the data subject with the ability to get access to his or her personal data that is being processed.

### Right to rectification

This right provides the data subject with the ability to ask for modifications to his or her personal data in case the data subject believes that this personal data is not up to date or accurate.

### Right to withdraw consent

This right provides the data subject with the ability to withdraw a previously given consent for processing of their personal data for a purpose.

### Right to object

This right provides the data subject with the ability to object to the processing of their personal data.

### Right to object to automated processing

This right provides the data subject with the ability to object to a decision based on automated processing.

### Right to be forgotten

Also known as right to erasure, this right provides the data subject with the ability to ask for the deletion of their data.

### Right for data portability

This right provides the data subject with the ability to ask for transfer of his or her personal data. As part of such request, the data subject may ask for his or her personal data to be provided back (to him or her) or transferred to another controller.

## How can you exercise your rights?

[Contact us here](https://wowthemes.net/support) with your GDPR request. Our ticket form has a special field called “GDPR Requests”, make sure you select it before submitting.

In most circumstances, our Company will provide subjects with a copy of the information they request free of charge. However, we are permitted to charge a “reasonable fee” when a request is manifestly unfounded, excessive or repetitive.

The fee must be based on the administrative cost of providing the information.

An alternative solution for excessive, unfounded or repetitive requests is to refuse to comply. In such case we will explain to the individual why we’re refusing to comply, and let them know of their right to appeal to the organisation’s supervisory authority.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. See more [here](http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf).

According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following: \- Users can visit our site anonymously. \- Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website. \- Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’ and can easily be found on the page specified above. \- You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes on our Privacy Policy Page. You can change your personal information by emailing us.

## COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States’ consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

We do not market to children under the age of 13 years old.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

Future changes to this Website’s Privacy Policy will be published on this page and, where appropriate, sent to you by email notification. Please check back frequently to read any updates or changes to this Privacy Policy.

## Business Info

WOW DEVELOPMENT, Bucuresti, Fiscal Code RO34450484, Contact.
